[Intro music]
Welcome to the Hydraulic Press Channel!
Today we have some strange things from 'Vat19'.
We have these, like, spit balls.
[Anni:] Boing, boing, boing!
[Lauri:] I have no idea what is the purpose of these, but they are quite hard to crush with your hands.
And...Yeah, I think they are quite interesting; especially with this special tool.
And then we have 'Thinking Putty', "poo-too", and this one is heat sensitive. Aha!
So it's like "meeerrrr".
It changes color when it gets hot or cold.
Yeah, but I think we are going to start with these.
And here are the same things before you add water, so they are quite small.
And here we go!
Yeah, that wasn't actually the hardest crushing that have made here. [Laughing]
Then the same thing, but more balls.
And here we go!
Uh-oh...
[Anni: laughing]
[Anni: slowed down] Boing, boing, boing, boing...
This is really strange, and a bit disgusting feeling thing now.
And here we go!
[Both laughing]
[Laughing continues]
[Lauri:] That was excellent!
[Wet sloshing sound]
[Music: William Tell's 'Overture']
[Music ends]
And then the first try with heat sensitive putty, or "poo-too". And...
...this changes color to yellow when it heats up, and I am not sure where is the limit, but if you hold your hand
there, like, one minute it gets yellow, so it's somewhere around 34 degrees Celsius, maybe.
...or 30.
But now we can see would the press heat it up enough to be yellow, and we are filming also with our thermal
camera to see what the temperature is even if it's not changing color.
And here we go!
[Laughing]
Just like giant Play-doh!
[Anni: laughing]
And now I have this thing, and I'm going to use same press tool as with those...water marbles, and then there
is about 5 mm gap on each side, so there is going to be shit load of pressure inside of that tube, and it would be
like forced to squirt up from there.
I think this looks like stomach from some anatomy book. Here is your throat, and here is your "shit-pipe".
[Anni: dying from laughter]
[Anni: exclaims in Finnish, laughing]
[Lauri:] And here we go!
[Laughing]
I think now it got hot because there is some yellow shit.
I have no idea how we are going to get that free from there.
[beeping]
I think I...[stutters]...could at least try the hammer, and if that's not going to work then I have to drill hole in the
bottom of that, and...try to get some air in there because I think there is vacuum under the pressing tool...
[Hammer strikes] No, it's...
[Hammering, clatters]
[Anni:] Uh-oh...
[Lauri: laughing]
Yeah, I was a bit worried that this would happen because this is, uh, cast iron and I noticed it...
after I had welded this there, and you cannot really weld cast iron.
Yeah, but I think that is all for today. Thank you for watching, and have a nice day!
[Outro music]
And for today's extra content we have this invisible dog. Even if you cannot see it it can still attack at any
moment, and we have to deal with it.
Liquid glass ashtray!
And if you liked the thermal camera footage, we have now new channel where everything is filmed with
thermal camera. Go check that out. It's in the end-screen coming soon.